downloadplanet.net 2012-06-01

# Our Privacy Policy - Shareme.com respects your right to privacy - Windows Shareware, Freeware, MP3, Games, DVD, Audio, Video Software

---|---  
| 

  * Business & Productivity Tools
  * Communications
  * Desktop Enhancements
  * Drivers
  * Educational
  * Games
  * Home & Personal
  * Internet
  * Multimedia & Design
  * Network Tools
  * Programming
  * Security
  * Utilities
  * Web Authoring

####  Top Downloads

  * XFreesoft DVD Ripper 

XFree DVD Ripper can convert DVD to any video...

  * iTake DVD Creator burner for Mac 

Perfect for any video to DVD conversion and DVD...

  * iTake DVD Creator 

iTake DVD Creator Burner is a powerful DVD...

  * iTake DVD Ripper 

Remarkable with fantastic speed and quality,...

  * MacVideo DVD Ripper 

Mac DVD Ripper can rip DVD to all popular video...

  * XFreesoft DVD Creator for Mac 

XFreesoft DVD Creator for Mac is a super easy...

  * MacVideo Video Converter 

Mac Video Converter is a powerful yet...

  * XFreesoft DVD Ripper for Mac 

If you are looking for DVD ripping software for...

  * MacVideo DVD Creator 

MacVideo DVD Creator is professional DVD...

  * iTake Video Converter 

iTake Video Converter is excellent video...

####  New Downloads

  * TeeChart Pro VCL/FMX 2012

100% VCL native Charting component library with...

  * dSHIFT Migrator for SharePoint 4.3.5.0

Have you used dSHIFT Migrator for SharePoint...

  * DWG to DXF Converter 201204 201204

DWG to DXF Converter is a batch DWG and DXF...

  * ID Card Creater 7.3.0.1

Professional design ID card creater software...

  * Corporate SMTP Server 5.23

Corporate SMTP Server is outgoing SMTP server...

  * Word PDF Converter 5.83

Word PDF Converter is an easy-to-use and...

  * Any DVD Cloner Platinum 1.1.7

Any DVD Cloner Platinum is an ultimate solution...

  * Sakina Privacy Protector 4.0.3

Sakina Privacy Protector is an ideal program...

  * Ares Galaxy Turbo Booster 6.0.9

Ares Galaxy Turbo Booster(AGTB) is a powerful...

  * BearShare Premium P2P 6.0.8

Bearshare Premium P2P is a free peer to peer...

####  Recent Searches

Advanced Id Creator Activation Key, Coupon For Breakoutbras, Outlaw Bike.., Acer Windows Vista Home Basic Service Pack, Anonymous Socks Proxy List, Advanced Html Tricks, Acer Windows Vista Home Basic, Advanced Flash Flip Book, Advanced Html Calendar, Iron Speed Designer Product Key, Acer Webcam Not Clear, Igi Part1 Game Cheat, Acer Travelmate 2490 Drivers, Advanced Find Replace Word 2007, Turbocad Deluxe Tutorial For Mac

| 

**Our Privacy Policy**

Shareme.com respects your right to privacy.

**What information do we collect?  
**Some technical information is collected automatically on each page in order to give us an idea of how people are finding our website, what technologies they are using to access it and which pages interest them. Each time a visitor loads a page from a website is counted as one 'page load'. About once a month we also collect the current set of page load information to look for trends, for example changes in the screen resolution, operating system or browser that is most often used. We take this information into account when planning for usability and accessibility in website design. We also collect information on how visitors reach our website, including search engine use, search key word use, and links referring visitors to our website. We use this information in our search engine optimisation and marketing strategies. Some examples of the information we collect and analyse include: the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, your operating system and screen resolution. We do not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors without their consent.  If you join a mailing list operated by us, you will be able to unsubscribe at any time. 

**Third-Party Advertisers**  
Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites. Our advertisers will generally store cookies on visitor's computers to record information including which advertisement they followed to reach the advertiser's website, and the date when they visited. Depending on the advertiser, cookies will expire (ie be automatically deleted) after different lengths of time.   
We use Google Adsense to support our site. Ads provided by Google AdSense, are targeted to be relevant to the content of the website and / or page they are on (ie they get the information from the website contents not the visitors themselves). Google Adsense uses cookies and web beacons to target and measure effectiveness of ads they serve on user pc. Here you can find [Google's Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) information.

**Software Listing**  
All the software programs published by shareme.com are provided by the third party software producers. Any questions complaints or claims related to the software should be directed to the appropriate Author or Company responsible for developing the software, not the staff working for shareme.com. All other trademarks are the sole property of their respective owners. The files and programs made available are indexed from servers all over the world. shareme.com makes no representations as to the content of such files and programs or that the files and programs are accurate, complete, virus-free or do not infringe the rights of any third party. If you found any software is in violation of any copyright or trademark, let us know and we will delete its listing from shareme.com site.

**Disclaimer**  
The files and programs made available are indexed from servers all over the world. shareme.com makes no representations as to the content of such files and programs or that the files and programs are accurate, complete, virus-free or do not infringe the rights of any third party. Each user is responsible to virus check any program downloaded from the site before installation. shareme.com is not responsible for any loss or damage resulting from users' downloading or use of any such programs or files.

**Links to Other Websites**  
This site contains links to other sites. shareme.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of other web sites before disclosing any personal information on another site. These other sites may independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to you. The Company is not responsible for any use of the information including click-stream data that you may create when using such third party web sites. You should carefully review the privacy policies of these third party web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information. 

**Contact us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, you can contact us

---|---  
  
Welcome to the ShareMe. Here you can free download windows shareware, freeware and demo versions of commercial software, games, mp3, dvd, audio, video programs. We do not share, host any crack, warez files either from mirrors or file hosting website rapidshare, depositfile, youtube. All software have posted by genuine software authors and we publish them, if you like it, buy the licensed full version or serial keys. Any questions, complaints or claims related to the software should be directed to the appropriate author or company responsible for developing the software, not the staff working for shareme.com
